There’s a rumour that you are the one who leaked the news of PEN-NUENG.
The person who committed the wrongdoing in this incident.
We will take the strongest possible action.
If you don't think about doing anything now,
You prepare to fall without ever getting up again.
I told you to go back.
The sound of your heart is beating so loudly.
It’s because you keep reminding yourself about your mistakes,
and you haven’t been able to face your true self for the past five years.
Please make me cry.
What you’re doing right now is
running away instead of putting up a fight.
By going back for a fresh start
isn’t running away.
But I have to live with the consequences of your fresh start.
If you can say this,
it means that you’re grown up now.
When my mom fell,
CCTV didn’t work?
Yes
Are you done crying?
What have I freaking done?
Judging from the way you moaned last night,
you can’t be feeling guilty now, can you?
You make me feel like a fool again.
You're not a fool.
You’re just being naive.
Although I believe that deep down,
you can sense that I'm someone
that's pretty special, right?
Let's go take a shower.
No, you go first.
I can't really get up.
Auditions for The Memory series are now open,
have you heard?
That doesn’t really concern me.
But it is because
I put your name on the audition list.
I don't wanna audition for this series.
That means that you really want to be a part of this series.
Again with the assuming things on your own.
Have you finished reading the original novel?
Not yet.
But finished reading the screenplay.
What if I…
I can just kick Sunny out,
and let you play instead?
Are you okay?
Didn't you waive your rights to Mr.Kongkiat?
I already told you.
In the end,
I will win.
Didn’t you say you wanted to get rid of those unfair connections?
And wanted to wipe out those shitty sponsors.
And why do you want to do the same again now?
So that means
you don't want to play this.
If I get through the audition myself,
then I'm okay.
I thought you only cared about getting revenge,
you’re unbelievable sometimes.
This is your next piece of homework.
Finish reading this novel.
And then we’ll talk.
Neat, done.
Okay, you can take it now.
Yes, sir.
Take this to his hand directly, okay?
Excuse-me?
Yes.
Where will you take the basket?
P’Boss wants me to take this to
TWO-O at the hospital.
At the Hospital?
Yes.
What happened?
Wave was acting as Sunny’s decoy.
He tricked me into meeting those sponsors
to talk about the project
that I would have a part in The Memory project.
But...
They forced me.
Those bastards did things to me.
Look at me now.
So what are you going to do now?
Have you ever thought about getting revenge?
Director
I don't think this contract is comprehensive enough.
Dream's operations are now at risk.
Do you want me to take care of it?
I'll take care of this myself.
Okay, sir.
So I'm excusing you today.
Yes.
I can't wait to see you tonight.
Director, sir.
There are customers asking to talk to you now.
Who?
Yes, I’ve arrived.
You’re Mr. two baht, right?
You can come this way.
Please.
Sit.
Normally,
I don't like people staring at me.
In the past, there was a teenager at the same age as you.
He also shared the same eyes as you.
He kept looking at my face.
He was also arrogant and aggressive.
You know how I handled him?
I pierced needles into his eyes.
And why don’t you think
how many needles do I need
for both of your eyes?
You couldn’t with your one needle.
How are you going to do that with your shaky hand?
Spike?
Just a cup of tea, you can hardly hold it well.
I'm a little late,
So I had old people like you waiting for me.
That’s so rude of me.
I think we should drink some tea while we’re waiting for the food.
Here is very famous for the tea.
Before asking me for a drink with you?
Shouldn’t you introduce yourself first?
What’s your name?
What is your real identity?
I'm sorry because I'm old and sloppy.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
When picking up or holding something, it starts to numb.
Then let me introduce myself.
I
am Director Arthur,
ATHIP VANITKITPAISARN
Executive Director of Dream Entertainment, sir.
Oh...
You’re that person who only made tiny profits
from the hotel business in America.
And now turn to invest in the entertainment business?
Compared to Mr. Songpol,
with your prostitution business,
oh I mean your gray-area business.
My hotel business income
was indeed just a fragment of yours.
Although nothing is going to last forever.
In the future
I might be able to make more money than you.
The person who kept running their mouth,
just because they think of themself as a young man.
Many of them have died before me.
Now that I’m looking at you,
I'm starting to worry for you.
Even though you are ancient,
but you’re still new in the industry.
May I?
The food is ready.
Yeah.
Come.
Don't go anywhere just yet.
Please hang around and help this old gentleman.
He’s too old so
he can't hold the chopsticks anymore.
Get out.
Let’s waste no time here.
I admire you
for the fact that you can sneak yourself into Dream’s
and that’s it.
I'm not stupid.
I thought you were smart enough, not stupid.
Not to follow in your mother's footsteps.
The reason why I invited you here today,
I have an offer for you.
Withdraw from The Memory Project,
and then leave Dream Entertainment.
And you shall have a good life,
be in a better place
where you should be.
This offer I never offered to anyone.
It's an opportunity, and you should take it.
Take this offer while you still can.
And one more thing.
It’s for the safety of the people around you.
Now, if I
still holding this cup of tea
and keep shaking like this.
Everyone is ready to believe that
I am what you say.
“This guy is an old man.
He can’t even hold his teacup well.”
It's just like your mother
that I've made people believe that
Pavinee has suicided.
I'm done for tonight.
Enjoy your meal.
Why did you take me to see him?
I want you to know the backer of the man you're taking revenge on.
What does he look like?
How vicious he is.
And he's targeting you.
What did he mean when he said that?
About…
Your mother.
The day my mother jumped off the building,
CCTV didn’t work.
The alarm system was shut down.
No witnesses saw her falling down the building.
So I can only suspect that he’s behind everything.
Do you think I'll end up like my mother,
if I don't do as he says?
What can I do for you?
You only need to focus on yourself.
I'll take care of this.
Hello, sir.
Is Director Arthur here?
Uhh..
Director Arthur had flown out for a meeting in America this morning,
There’s no scheduled return date yet.
Oh!
Ow!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry, sorry too.
P’Kajorn!
Hey!
Where are you in such a rush?
It's Sky,
He called someone who was waiting to meet us in the office right now.
He said that Director Arthur asked him to see us.
Who are you?
Oh…
I saw it over there
and there’s hot water too.
So I just cooked this myself and eating it.
If you have kimchi,
it would be so much better.
This is mine!
Hm?
Uncle, no!
Oh, P’Sun
Hi, P’Kajorn.
Here I am.
Here is soda for you.
Nice! Thank you.
Who is this?
He is Uncle Suchat,
he’s a new assistant manager.
He was sent to assist you.
Really? It looks like he only eats and sleeps.
My new assistant manager?
Have a look at this.
The press conference for the launch of The Memory The Series.
Why do we not know about any of this?
Oh?
What's going on?
Director Arthur just flew to America this morning
then why suddenly…
This is considered the biggest project of the year
of ours with this series.
And it's a project that Sunny
will finally get to play as a lead actor.
I hope everyone in the press will continue
to support and follow his work.
And also, please support the newer gen in our company as well.
How prepared are you, Sunny,
I heard that the casting was very intense.
Yes, sir, it was really intense.
I'm very ready now.
And now I’m trying to get in better shape and
we’re also doing workshops now.
May I?
I heard there was a big investor who
co-invested in this project,
and now global platforms have
been lining up to acquire it.
Can you share when it will be released?
That's him, guys. Mr.Songpol of SP group.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Are you alright?
Sir Songpol, come this way, please.
Hello again, everyone.
Hello, and thank you very much.
Consider this a business that
I'm not skilled.
So I'm still a freshman.
If there is anything wrong…
You must have seen the press conference.
After the event, there will be a private dinner for the investors.
I am summoned there too.
I'll share you the location
Hey, uncle.
You don't have to follow me all the time.
I don't have any work today.
Who said that I was following you? I need to use the restroom.
Oh!
I like simple things.
simply the best.
Ouch!
It must be painful to be in a car accident.
Anyway, get treatment nicely before the first day on set.
Please take good care of him.
Even if his one hand isn’t working that well now.
Although he’s great with his mouth and other things too.
Look at him.
This might be a flawed product,
but I can assure you the quality is top notch.
You really know me so well.
Can I have some wine?
What do you want to drink?
Liquor or good wine?
Anything is fine, sir.
Great.
Here you go.
Okay.
I'll have to excuse myself.
Please feel free to make yourself at home.
How's the business going lately?
It’s nice.
Better than before, actually.
I'm glad to hear.
I’ll excuse myself to the toilet just a second.
Don't go for fae too long.
He must be excited still.
It's okay.
That I can teach.
You can do as much as you want.
Go hard or go home, right?
Easy, go easy on him.
I got it on video, will send it soon.
So this is how you’re going to play me?
Sorry to disturb you during your private time, sir.
Just say it.
TWO-O spied on us and secretly sent the information to Sun.
Sun?
And who the hell is Sun?
It's just Dream's ordinary trainee.
This is him.
An ordinary trainee?
An ordinary trainee who’s that damn director Arthur
always have him by his side.
And you said that he’s just an ordinary trainee?
I heard that he’s been talking about his backer a lot,
so his backer is actually Director Arthur?
Um,
Well, then...
What about you?
What can you do for me?
I want his great backer
to see what it’s like to get in my way.
I don’t want things to end well for him.
Can you do that for me?
Yes, sir.
well
I'm getting tired of him.
Can you prove it to me?
Can you do it?
You can use my belt.
No one will hear about this.
What are you waiting for?
So I can continue to have fun outside.
What’s it gonna be?
Yes, sir.
Hey!
Don't.
Let me go.
Hey!
Let go! Let go of me!
Let me go!
Hey!
Do you know that
you just broke one of my toys?
Do you have any idea?
Me?
Don't make excuses.
You broke one of my toys.
You go to find another piece for me.
I’m kind enough to let it slide.
I want that Arthur’s boy,
and that cute one too.
He’s not dead yet.
Get up.
Stop!
I don’t want any bruises on his face. He’ll get upset.
Where did you take TWO-O to?
You almost die and
still worried about others?
I won’t let TWO-O die easily.
He’ll be tortured for a long time.
For the fact that he chose the wrong side.
What do you want?
Ever since I stole your money
I’ve been paranoid the whole time.
I'm afraid that one day you will come and take your money back.
Because I know that
the you’re the type to never let things go.
But you never mess with me once.
I thought that you were already dead.
And then all of a sudden, you came back.
I have to ask you
what do you want from me?
You were the reason why my brother died,
and mother too.
Is this reason enough?
Dead?
People like you don't feel anything,
no matter who lives or dies.
Who said you don't feel things?
The reason that your brother and your mother are dead,
what the fuck does this have to do with me?
I didn't go and kill them.
If you want revenge so badly,
take it out on yourself.
The reason you took my name to use,
isn’t it because you feel guilty?
With what you did to me.
Yeah, you can think of whatever you want.
But I’m going to warn you
about your revenge that
not only will it bring you trouble,
but it will cause trouble for people around you as well.
What are you going to do?
What can I do, Sun?
Aside from warning you for the last time.
Let him go.
Just go.
Yes, P’Sun
I’m done filming.
How about P’Kajorn?
He’s here too.
We’ll be home soon.
Hey, Sky, get in the car.
It's okay. I'll go with the crew van.
You should go back to Angie.
See you later.
Really?
Oh, do you miss us?
No, nothing.
Then go home safely, okay?
Tell me once you’re home.
Yes, I'll tell you once I’m home.
The van is here.
Yes, see you.
Hello!
But I’m going to warn you
about your revenge that
not only will it bring you trouble,
but it will cause trouble for people around you as well.
How are you, Two baht?
Sia, sir.
Do you know why Jay went to America?
And does he know that
Mr.Kongkiat had held the press conference for the launch of the series.
Or is he going to give up?
I don't know,
why Jay would do that?
But I still believe
that my Jay isn’t
a coward.
And there’s you,
becoming his one and only Mr. Three Baht.
Why is it three baht?
Because of my Jay,
he has put that thing into you.
So that makes you a Mr. three baht now.
Mr. Three baht
I was just kidding.
I don't want you to stress yourself out.
Mr. Two baht,
come on.
I'll buy you some drinks.
I’m going to get it to you.
Mr. Three baht
Hey, go. Let's go.
Hey, get in the car.
Who are you guys?
You don't need to know.
I told you to get in the car.
What the fuck do you want?
Bastard, stop asking questions.
What are you playing?
May I join?
It’s none of your business, old man.
Take this.
Uncle?
Let's go.
More of them will come for sure.
Go.
Jay asked me to take care of you while he’s away.
Jay?
Yep.
And when will he come back?
Whoa,
Have this guy ever told anyone where he's going?
Or who knows what he is doing?
Just now, you said as like
you knew those people.
It's just gangsters
that were hired by an influential group of investors.
These guys are willing to do anything for money.
Sky, where are you?
Haha, he’s with me.
I will send the location to you.
I want you to come alone.
If you dare bring anyone with you,
or ask anyone for help.
This kid's a dead meat.
You’re with P’Kajorn, right?
Good.
Don't go anywhere alone, okay?
I give you twenty minutes.
If you're even a minute late…
Okay, see you.
Uncle, I’m going to buy some water.
One for me, please. Anything sweet will do.
P’Sun?
I came.
Now you guys can let him go.
Calm down.
Sit down first,
so that we can talk nicely.
He’d like you two to be in good condition.
P'Sun, P'Sun.
P’Sun!
P’Sun
Sky!
Dummy.
Hey!
Jay, please, don't.
Jay
The members of the board have filed
a request to remove Director Arthur
from Dream Entertainment.
No price is too high
for revenge for me.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm taking everything from you.
Including Director Arthur.
Don’t take your eyes off me.